see participants joining very fast like
we have 13 participants right now uh let
us allow another two minutes and then
maybe I can give a quick brief on the
agenda how the flow is going to be and
uh how we are going to proceed with the
discussion today which all of us have
been looking forward to okay
um all right I'll put myself on
mute
in the interest of everyone's time and
uh uh in favor of everyone who has
joined on time uh we will uh get started
in about a
minute uh but in the mean while just to
give you a background of what we are
going to do today uh I think some of you
have been trying to raise your
hands um we are keeping the chat box
disabled because that is going but we
are keeping the Q&A enabled so if you
have any questions any suggestions
please type type your questions and
suggestions in the Q&A box
okay can someone type a question on the
Q&A box I would like to see if we are
getting the questions from your
end hello I got it yes thank you Rajiv
is that Raj thank you
thank you very
much all right I got that question
similarly everyone uh the moment you see
questions uh you have questions please
type it in the Q&A box we are going to
address all the questions towards the
end of the session the session is going
to begin with a quick intro and then I'm
going to give you some uh information
which is very crucial uh followed by
I'll pass it on to Mr Manish who is on
the call and he's going to give uh self-
introduction of himself followed by a 1H
hour discussion about the solution we
will go through the product specs
illustration examples a lot has to be
covered and after that we will have a
Q&A session wherein all the questions
that you will have put it in the Q&A box
I'm going to take those questions and Mr
Manish is going to address
those okay now I would like to uh
understand if everyone is okay with
English or do you want a mix of English
and Hindi if anyone if uh you can just
put it in the Q&A box
please anything is okay some people are
comfortable only in English so what we
can do we can keep it as a mix of both
okay so everyone whoever is comfortable
in English they can understand as well
as Hindi they can also
understand all
right now um let's see what is the
time okay we have five minutes
past we are five minutes past our a
lotted time uh let us start the
discussion so um I am I'm guessing I had
had a chance to discuss and had a
session with all of you before the
holidays but if I have not been uh if I
have not had a chance to speak to you
before the holidays and this is the
first time that we are interacting uh
welcome everyone thank you for joining
thank you thank you for taking the time
out to join us today I am Swati I take
care of the can Network I'm heading the
same and I'm responsible to make sure
that your journey through the entire can
uh Network whether it is as a partner
whatever queries you have help regarding
any collateral or Solutions or your
client's Journey I'll make sure that U
it goes seamless so that is my goal now
um I would not like to spend a lot of
time on my introduction rather let's
move on to the next part we are going to
keep the session in three parts one is
uh the initial introduction second is
the product specs we will run few polls
in
between whether you are getting the gist
of what we are explaining and then we
will uh end up end the call with a Q&A
session
okay before we start the call um there
are two surprising surpr incentive
surprises that I have for you the first
incentive that I'm going to mention
right now and the second one you'll have
to wait till the end of the discussion
Okay so today the agenda of the
discussion is uh to discuss the regular
payout or the regular income solution
which is Sunjoy by
sunlife sunlife has been in the market
for more than a century so there are no
doubts that it is a very robust uh
solution and it has history of over a
century so you can imagine that it is
double a rated it is it is a it is a
tried and tested company as well as the
solutions of it are very well tried and
tested Ed now based on my discussion
with most of you I think I had some 50
meetings before the holidays uh based on
my discussion I
understood say a lot of you were
interested in knowing what are the
Saving Solutions that we provide as
Continental what are some of the
investment solutions that we can provide
so basis on that feedback we thought why
not start with this solution now why
this solution is important Manish is
going to take you through
Manish Sharma has been with the
organization for a very long time and
why I like why he is the speaker today
you will get to know very soon once he
starts explaining you the solution but
he himself has sold the solution several
times n India may but macius Africa and
in different parts he will highlight
himself with all the examples very good
solution with all like very um it's a
multi-purpose can be used for different
needs of the clients and how to position
it Manish has himself done it so he is
the best person who can actually guide
you through now coming to that part
Manish is going to self introduce
himself once uh in the next uh part but
as you can imagine with all the
expertise that he holds with all the
experience on the ground experience that
he holds he has been willing to actually
help out now as we go through the
session the I would I'm going to run a
quick survey in the background we will
share the link with you
shortly as the solution proceeds whoever
shares one or at least one or two client
profiles in your mind for whom the
solution fits the best we are going to
select the top five clientele that comes
into your mind Manish is going to help
you end to endend in closing the cases
for the clients he'll handhold you and
with his experience you are definitely
going to close the case so long as the
case is genuine the client's interest
and needs are actually meeting we are
going to close it so that is an
incentive wherein you are going to get
manisha's expertise on a onetoone
personal basis so I am urging and I am
encouraging all of you to please make
the most out of this opportunity make
sure that you know while the session is
proceeding think of all the client that
you have and then we are going to share
the link with you share the client
profile details that the link is going
to ask you and after the session we are
going to pick up uh Manish and us we are
going to discuss and select the top five
and then we are going to rever to
you one to one
discussion and end to end
help
okay any questions that you have please
put it in the Q&A box throughout the
discussion we are going to address all
of that during the last 20 to 30 minutes
now before without any further Ado I
would like to invite Mr Manish Sharma to
take on the call from here
on thank you Manish for uh coming and
sharing your time with us and all your
expertise with the team over here thank
you STI thank you very much uh for a
brief introduction and uh opening the
session session for all of us and first
of all good afternoon to everyone uh to
come on board for this uh session and uh
I'm your host for today Manish Sharma
and let me just uh give you a brief
introduction about myself before we
going to start with a poll here uh so
this is my profile on your screen I'm
Manish uh and I'm in this business of
family protection insurance uh wealth
protection
keyman protection Solutions so basically
starting from insurance to the financial
uh uh background providing uh customers
with the financial solution customized
Solutions I'm in this business for last
23 years now uh my entire background has
been through Banking and insurance field
so naming few uh though I again I belong
to India my native place is japur but uh
I'm in macius for last 10 plus years now
and uh I started
my career with Modi Telecom then Banks
like IC City Bank HSBC and I was with
Max life in India for seven plus years
worked in different different cities
from jodpur to gooda to oraba to Bombay
and then move to macius so I have a
decent experience globally now uh
meeting clients providing them Solutions
so this is my background and I'll be
providing you the insight about this
exclusive product offered by sunlife so
before moving further on the product
side uh I would like uh a colleague
Nisha who is in the background to start
with a poll if I'm correct
STI that's right so give us a minute we
will just enable the
poll so you can participate in the poll
which will help us to understand what
are your expectations and
all
so everyone you should be able to write
in a single sentence what are you
expecting at the end of this call
session
sayu you want to learn what do you want
to learn what are you expecting out of
this
session you can just write a single word
or a sentence it's it's up to
you so we have 1 minute uh for this PO
yeah we have received seven responses
very good very good all
right another 15
seconds come on
guys okay uh
Sati okay thank you very much for your
participation in the poll uh we'll be
having U one more poll in the mid of the
session uh for you so please do
participate so that we can understand
you better and your expectations
so now uh I will start about this
product so I'll give you
idea we can't interact right now but
definitely in the question and answer
we're going to answer more about
this I'm not a teacher so as
an I've been into
sales
[Music]
few selective
products
mix
and plan
solution
sfc
Max
Reliance mostly clients advis guaranted
income plan Solutions
offer very difficult to analyze what
will happen to the money they are
investing even advisers are not
confident simple
thing
rment
external it impacts a lot guaranted
income plan
Solutions why people are liking them a
lot reason being because there's an inbu
guarantee of capital at least you will
going to receive this much amount so it
is easy for advisers to sell it is easy
for client to understand so this plan
today we are talking about it is a mix
and match of those so first important
aspect of this plan okay this is offered
by sunlife sunlife is an 154 year old
group Canadian
orig in a simple way they are called of
Canada
same thing sunlife is known as LC of
Canada 154 years business highly credit
rated they have an entity in Hong Kong
sunlife Hong Kong which
is7 year old in Hong Kong itself Hong
Kong Hong
Kong
USD
offer directly distrib worldwide 155
countries
now continue paying after fifth year
today I have an income but I don't know
whether it will be there after 10 years
or not or after 15 years or not to have
client shorter period they can imagine
if I come and say you okay you have to
pay premium only for two years you're
very happy okay I can imagine next two
years I have to pay or you have to pay
for 5 years you can easily imagine why
people are investing in mutual fund a
lot reason being there is no commitment
that you have to keep on paying for 15
years 20 years and if you surrender in
between there will be a penalty people
are investing in mutual fund because it
is giving a slightly better return than
Insurance uh policy savings plan then uh
there is flexibility if you want to exit
you can take out the returns same thing
this plan offers that you have a freedom
of your plan so this plan has one
important component which is guaranteed
income so this plan offers you a
guaranteed income you can decide your
income based on the returns which we
will going to calcul Cate and send it to
you which which is in the range of 6%
perom now we'll come on how it is
calculated then multiple settlement
options are there you can decide how you
want to take money you want to take
money as a lumpsum you want to take
money as a regular income for rest of
your life you want to take money as a
regular income and then withdraw the
lump suum you have multiple settlement
options available there death benefit
death benefit in the sense whatever you
are paying in case of death the amount
which accumulates can be paid to the
beneficiary if you have not chosen other
settlement options which I will going to
explaines tax planning so again uh it
offers as a def tax
savings same thing this plan has income
generate that will be as taxable as
other investment plans in
India at that time you have a choice
simp now what is Pension
Plan fix decided by
Insurance 55 60
65 in case of your death 5 years 10
years
fix
but
terminology early retirement suppose
decide I want to retire at age 50 or I
want to retire at age 45 I don't want to
continue up to AG
6th 7th 8th 10th 15 20
Dey tax planning
Bas then it will be taxable in your hand
as the money keeps on
growing
income ta same applicable for this plan
also which is accidental care benefit
now accidental care
benefit for any reason due to an
accident where they are not able to
perform daily three duties daily three
duties they cannot take bath on their
own they are dependent on someone for
eating they cannot go to
toilet langage let's say because of
accident someone goes intoa now they are
into vegetable
State times insurance company
immediately pay client which is insured
yeah $1.25 million maximum whichever is
less immediately pay or policy as it is
continue
is being is an insurance
company intergenerational wealth
transfer important point PL as a
succession plan Legacy
transfer
120 Years of
theur Legacy of succession plan
let your next Generation enjoy
this
Bas now short premium payment
term easily
imagine they can imagine their income
for next two years or 5 years
client gu options guaranted cash
valuec
third comp minimum guaranteed cash
value of a
surrender option revisionary bonus
revisionary bonus non guaranted but de
every year insurance company has to
decare revisionary bonus non guaranted
but declared on the performance of
insurance
company it becomes
guaranted third option terminal bonus
terminal bonus non guaranted again it is
based on insurance
comp
now revisionary bonus or terminal bonus
deare on the basis of
investment participating and
nonparticipating
policies
policies participating policies so
nonp
participating polies Insurance
participate
sameti Insurance Sun participating fund
$137 billion participating
fure
5% volatility comes
from Equity now as I said at the start
China or us entered into war India will
suffer Ukraine and Russia entered into
war India is suffering Market goes up
and down and the investment stock market
it will going to fluctuate it can be
higher it can be lower depending on the
market news but when there is a little
investment in equity Equity investment
fluctuation maximum
investment money market instruments
bonds cash andh
equal how it works
return is very stable in this plan now
important
aspect of
this guaranted terms 13 years break
guaranted terms means only guaranted
cash value forget about revisionary and
terminal bonus
guarante
actual return including revisionary and
terminal bonus de insurance company and
every year they are doing very well
which I will going to show you later to
break even
period years and five years that means
in s
years
as for five pay and for two pay it is in
six years to Peace of Mind client
fluctuate against Indian
currency
example
against dollar
against
83 doar is around
95 going to get extra money
in
comp there's no currency risk
now
premium and
inally
totally depends on client Freedom
Cent minimum
start we can start withdrawing or
depending minimum
premium
which depending on how you
convince
intergenerational weth
transf
until
unrr
next
next liquidity
transfer death benefit settlement he
benefit
settlement as a
client
I
regular
income
death benefit settlement option
basically accidental Care
Plus
dep
more than 200
Cars
situ lost their
limbs premi so let's example
policy into 10
times immediately Insurance
comp
immediately
Maxim $1.25
million
maximum 1.25
million th% which is 10 times of total
premium
immediately
now accidental care benefit loss of
independent existence this daily
duties
understand
that scenario during premium payment
term so let's take example
ex up to
Maxim the maximum is
$200,000 installments Off plan as it is
continue 10 times of total premium Max
1.25
million
Ur now additional benefit for the payer
benefit basically
because of accident passed away before
age 65 because
of then additional benefit for five pay
premium which is premium holiday though
secondy
gued cash value
accus
for that kind of a scenario client has
an option to take premium holiday so
this option is available here to opt for
a premium
holiday
now
example we have another Poll for you uh
which our colleague will going to run
another poll just we would
appreciate respon this so that we can
understand
expectation and can we please have a
poll yeah Nisha is going to run it
shortly yeah up screen me you will you
should be able to see two
questions and while you are answering
these question questions just wanted to
let you
know in the last 20 to 30 minutes of our
Q&A
session
we have 28 participants or only
participants I
enage second yes or no and these are
very important questions what do you
think
experience all of you are very
experienced dollar based Solutions India
how is
the do you think there is a market for
dollar based
Solutions background question how how is
our solution different from what India
is offering to which is very obvious is
dollar based
solution
but in the
me please respond to the poll and then
we'll close the poll thank
you okay so we have completed two
minutes uh
STI thank you very much for your answers
everyone so now we'll move to the second
illust so maybe then you will have more
questions
VIP
because so a 45y old
person uh nonsmoking
resident in
India 5 year option
choose and he's paying $20,000 every
year for next five years
[Applause]
$20,000
8331 million1
milon accidental care benefit
C
651 million
immediately because of an accident $1
million
immediately as
it
he can easily get $6,000 per
year cash withdrawal amount $6,000 per
year so let's take example Cent 51
start
already withdraw
already hi Manish sorry to interrupt
there has been a request let's try to
cover some parts in English because
people some of them are not
understanding Hindi
numbers okay so uh okay let me start
again uh so this plan is basically
client has chosen to pay
$20,000 per year for next 5 years now
$20,000 equivalent to INR is around
$675,000 uh 16 l7500 ,000 rupees per
anom so in total 5 years client is
paying $100,000 which is equivalent to
83 lakhs in total in 5 years now client
has to pay only for 5 years nothing to
be paid after that even if client wants
to pay sixth year they cannot so they
have to pay if they have chosen to pay
five years they have to pay only for
five years now this client said that I
want immediate annuity after I finish my
premium payment term so that is from
sixth year client is eligible to get
$6,000 per year $6,000 per year means if
I calculate in INR it comes to around uh
4 lak9 5 lakh rupees uh per year so
client is getting 5 lakh rupees per year
for Lifetime lifetime means till the
time client is alive now you can suggest
client okay this client is up age 80
client says okay I'm already 80 years
old I don't need money more than this I
already have enough money I have
withdrawn so how much he has withdrawn
up to age 80 is
$180,000 he paid only $100,000 he has
already withdrawn
$180,000 and he still have
$189,000 available as lumsum in the
policy which means he paid 100,000
already took 180,000 and still have
189,000 now he can decide to withdraw
this
$189,000 as lumsum or he can choose to
say can you transfer this 189 into two
policies between two of my kids equally
so insurance company can uh design a new
policy dividing the benefit equally to
the kids and they can continue the
policy and they can decide their own
withdrawals when they want from which
year they want or which age they want
they have a choice or client can
withdraw this money and use it for
himself so if you see from age uh from
age 51 till age 80 total amount which he
is getting is
$369,000 against $100,000 paid out of
which this 6,000 is a withdrawal every
year still there is a guaranteed
component available there is a
revisionary bonus which is withdrawn
because client is taking withdrawals
every year and there is a terminal bonus
which is declared by insurance company
so total client is getting
$369,000 or client says I don't want to
surrender the policy let him take $6,000
till the time when he wants to take if
you see actually he is withdrawing up to
age
120 so this plan gives that benefit like
pension plan or any other such plans
available in the market Indian
market contr Cent
polic but here plan continues when
client is alive plan even continues when
client is not alive because let's take
this client said he whenever I die
please transfer this policy in my wife's
name she will become insured so let's
take a example client dies at age 70 he
has already taken 120 now this policy
gets transferred to wife wife will
continue withdrawing this
$6,000 plan will not come to an end but
if client has not choosen the second
insured in case of death the plan will
come to an end 120 he has already
withdrawn 136 will be paid as a lumpsum
and the policy will come to an end so
there are multiple death benefit options
client can choose to be paid lumsum in
case of death or it can continue even if
I die first benefit is this second
illustration same thing I have done 45
years old paid for five years
$220,000 $100,000 paid in 5 years but
this client says I don't want money from
my age 51 I want to retire at age 61 can
you pay me then so instead of 6,000
client will be getting $113,000 per year
not 6,000 because he was withdrawing
early he was getting 6,000 he's keeping
the incubation period of 15 years he's
getting higher money he's getting
$13,000 every year let's say this client
again until age 180 he has already
withdrawn
$260,000 and still $21,000 is available
as lumpsum paid only
$100,000 pay
L he is withdrawing higher than the
other client who started withdrawing
from age 51 because you are keeping
longer period for your nut to start it
is growing at a faster rate you're
getting more returns so if you compare
here with this client at age 80 total
withdrawal for this client was 369
because he started from age 51 the
withdrawal for this client total
withdrawal in age 80 is
461 because he kept a incubation period
of 15 years where the other client kept
incubation period of 5 years so this
plan gives that kind of a benefit same
thing let's take an example for a uh
2-year
uh plan where client is paying $50,000 a
year so $50,000 a year into Indian
currencies compare around 42 lakh rupees
uh per year paid for next two years so
total again $100,000 paid
$100,000 this client says I want
withdrawal immediately after my premium
payment again he can get
$6,000 till whatever age he or she wants
to withdraw so if you see in 80 years
time and this client is 80 he has
already with drawn
$198,000 and still $88,000 is available
as
lumsum so client has that kind of a
benefit in this plan now before going on
the other part I'm just changing my
screen and taking you to few
illustrations which I have done for some
of the
clients okay so now I'm sharing with the
live examples a few clients which uh I
have done this client is in macius his
name is Rajiv 57 years old last year
I've done the policy I met this client
so this client told me Manish I have $1
million 1 million around
fix
dep so he had a fixed deposit of 8
around 8 CR which is $1 million
equivalent so he told me Manish I can
give you this money but my requirement
is that I need
$5,000 per month as an expense of my
house in bishes he has other incomes and
all but uh I want $5,000 perom uh per
month to maintain expenses of Maisha
house I said okay so I proposed him give
this $1 million in 2 years which is
$500,000 per year for next 2 years and
then just wait for two years third year
onwards you will start getting
$60,000 now $60,000 every year which is
around $5,000 per month for rest of his
life so I told him okay when you are age
80 you won't be working that much you
can transfer this benefit to your next
Next Generation he has two daughters one
is in Canada and one is working with her
with him in bishes so you can transfer
these benefits to daughter because in
any case you will transfer all your
assets to your daughters he said yes so
I said Till the time you are at enjoy
the benefit he's getting $60,000 morous
expenses taken care $1.2 million 26
million he has already withdrawn and he
still have
$89,000 available as lumsum again $1
million total he's getting
$269,000 now another argument which you
can get from client is that client can
say fix depit why I need to keep money
here agree this client was also getting
in fixed deposit and at certain stage
fcnr fixed deposit in foreign currency
rate increased to 5% 5 and a half% also
she said Manish I can get 5 and half% in
fcnr whereas you are giving me 6% here
what is the benefit or for putting money
here I told him one thing very clearly
fixed deposit maximum you can do is for
three years or five years not more than
that because once interest rate
fluctuates you cannot continue as a
fixed deposit rate will go down or rate
will go up whereas here this is for
Lifetime you are getting at the rate of
6% which none of the fixed deposit can
pay fixed
deposit
but here this is guaranteed for
Lifetime continue so what he did he put
$1 million it's already one and half
years from next year by end of this year
he will start getting 60 okay next of uh
third year onwards he'll start getting
$60,000 per year and his policy
continues and he has appointed his wife
as a second insured so in any case he he
dies in any age this 60,000 will
continue to be paid to wife and wife can
continue this policy and appoint
daughter as a second insured in the
policy example Cent 57 a
client Ken Zimbabwe based client Mr
Richard 34 years very
young I
think
he has a good income so same I proposed
him $1 million which is $500,000 to year
pay
to around 8 CR he has paid in two years
time but he is Young so what I suggested
him that wait for 15 years because you
are young there's no need for money for
him he's still earning very good so 16th
year onwards instead of withdrawing
immediately start taking money from 16th
year on which is
$150,000 $150,000 per year if I
calculate on today's currency in INR it
is around uh s 1.25 CR he can withdraw
every year for himself and I told him
keep on withdrawing till the time you
want let's take till your old age age 75
let's take age
75 he paid $1 million he has already
withdrawn $3.9 million which is four
times of what he has paid and he still
has around $2 million in the policy so
he paid $ million and he has total
amount withdrawn is $5.8
million which is six times of what the
he has paid and that to this income is
guaranteed for him for life or instead
of taking this $2 million he can decide
let me transfer it to my son X
percentage to the younger one X to the
eldest one and the middle one X percent
is they can continue whatever
withdrawals they want to make from their
policy so this plan gives that kind of a
freedom to him yet to I have given you
example of one for macius and one for
Zimbabwe now another example I want to
give you last year which I did it in
India in Pune so I met a client uh
client young he just in his 35 age 35 B
so
his grandfather but the zeroy old child
grandfather so we met him so I asked him
what kind of a educational solution you
have done for your
grandchild I just started a mutual fund
uh investment of 2 lakhs per month 2
lakhs per
month in to 12 so he's paying 24 lakhs
perom I said is there any specific
period you'll be paying well no no I
will continue paying till the time he is
of age going for a higher studies so
he'll be needing money because we need
to send our grandchild to abroad for
studies dat every Indian is wishing to
send their child for higher studies so I
said okay but can you guarantee that it
will grow to that pace is said it's
mutual fund it can grow definitely I
said okay but if you need money for
child school fees can you get it from
there well no I can't I said if I give
you a solution where you have to pay
only for five years and by the time your
child start going to school they will
pay you the school fees also for your
child and when he goes for higher
studies we will pay the higher studies
uh fees also whichever country you want
to send he said okay tell me so 2 lakhs
per month which is 24 lakhs I have
advised him the same amount to be paid
for 5 years which comes to
$330,000 per year so if you see here
$30,000 per year which is
$2,650 per month so monthly option so
he'll be paying $2,650 per month which
is in 5 years paying
$150,000 if you compare it and convert
to Ina it will come to similar amount
which he was paying for mutual fund he
said okay and I told him when sixth year
onwards we'll start paying you $10,000
every year which is school fees for your
grandchild so
$10,000 is around
800,000 8 lakh 800 830,000 rupees uh per
year India May if you go to even best of
best school you can easily cover within
the that kind of a school fees 8 lakh
rupees which we are paying every year
for school fees of the child let's State
child is 18 years old you have already
paid $130,000 for a school fees and you
still have
$132,000 available for higher studies
this amount you can use as a lumpsum to
pay the fees for higher studies for next
two years or three years depending on
which country you are choosing to send
your
grandchild in the mutual fund where he
was paying 2 lakhs per month he was not
having that kind of a benefit to get
school fees and as well as the higher
studies fees in this plan he has that
benefit where he can pay the school fees
as well as higher studies fees also he
was so happy with this he stopped his
mutual fund and he invested in this
money in this plan so depending on
client situation and what client is
looking for you can advise this plan
accordingly so this is a multi-purpose
plan depending on client requirement
benefit flexibility customizable you can
do it guarantees be bonuses be
accidental care benefit be everything is
there I'll just want to share one slide
Investments run so that you can
easily have a
understanding just allow me one
minute
presentation but to explain you where
the money gets invested and security how
it comes so this plan as I said
$33.7 billion
fund a and above
a insured grade bonds 67% Triple B 30%
and 3 plus he BB lower credit rated
investment uh quality assets and asset
type if we talk 47% in debt security 29%
in mortgages and Loans 6% in cash and
cash equalent and only 5% in equity
Securities so the risk of the uh bonus
is going down is very low geographical
distribution wise 48% in Canada 37% in
US 9% in Europe 3% Asia and others and
industry-wise if you look at the
industries whether there's covid whether
there is war anything these industries
will still grow financial sector Public
Utilities real estate government
agencies energy it Communication Service
Health Service all these industries
where they invest money so the security
is very high
here now going back on the
presentation now what is in it for
you 2
years
14.4
take $5,000
14.4% which is
$2,160
which is
$5,400 first
second what you can earn out of this
that's your
benefit thank you very much for this and
um uh there is is uh another poll I
believe
STI we will run that poll after the Q&A
so let's head to the Q&A and then now we
are on question and answers
session specifically within the time
limit definitely we going to answer
or questions definitely we're going to
rever back via email or via phone call
to
you
all right I have the list of questions
Manish I'll pass it on to
you okay
um let me first of
[Music]
all
right first of
all in different different forms
like how is this solution different okay
how is this solution for example Mr J Mr
the same
question simar
solution you can only sell denominated
products USD Solutions
India you cannot sell third thing India
the plans which are available are
Pension Plan not annuity plan where
there is a flexibility p Pion plan is
basically as I said in the presentation
you have to keep on paying money for a
certain period of time and then you can
start getting pension from age 55 60 or
65 what you choose till the time you are
alive or for a certain guaranteed period
here this plan gives flexibility
withdrawals are for Lifetime till the
time you are alive and you can transfer
to your next Generation so there is no
comparison between this plan and uh the
plants available in India the plant
available in India right now are the
guaranted income plans
which you pay for 5 years or 8 Years or
lumsum or you pay for certain number of
years and you start getting guaranteed
income for 15 years 20 years or 30 years
or up to age 70 and then there is an
insurance component into that but that
works only up to certain age not for
lifetime so there is a difference
between the plan that's why people are
liking and investing and mostly people
those who want to keep certain money
invested into hard currency which is
dollar currency those kind of a people
are the right profile for this solution
not everyone again if you start going to
every client U with dollar based product
solution Vision regarding the investment
in abroad your future may they are not
the right client fit to this if you have
100 clients not all the clients will
going to fit with this Prof kind of a
product maybe 10 or 15 clients 10 or 15%
of your product uh total client
portfolio is the right fit for this kind
of a
product okay uh before I move on to the
next question I would like to share the
link uh of uh client
profile initially before the call
started I had mentioned that if you
share after now that you have understood
the product we are still discussing the
Q&A and we will clarify your queries but
meanwhile whatever you have understood
I'm sure sure it must have come that
okay this solution seems like a good fit
for this client of
M please share the client profiles with
us Manish is going to select top five
profiles and he will help you end to end
Cas
close if that client profile meets I
mean if our solution meets the need of
that client profile okay I'm putting on
that link on your screen scen right now
and you should be able to fill the form
and just few details about the clients
that will help us uh short list the
client
profiles okay now moving on to the next
uh set of
questions Mr jyam has asked couple of
questions I'll take up his questions um
accidental care is applicable only on
accident can a person become informed
due to an illness will this benefit be
applicable no only in case of accidental
uh that's why the name is accidental
care benefit this is applicable only in
case of accidental if person becomes
disabled and not able to perform minimum
three daily duties so not because of
illness it has to be because of
accident okay next question if the
person dies and has not opted for
continuation of the policy what happens
so in that case uh whatever the
surrender benefit is will be paid to the
benefician policy comes to an
end
is there any medical restrictions to
apply for this policy there is no
medical restriction because this is not
a life insurance plan or a medical plan
it's it's an investment plan so there is
no restriction country restriction or
medical restriction but yes we have to
be aware the person is already disabled
and not able to perform if you're taking
Plan in his or her name that is not
right so plan person has to be healthy
wealthy to apply for a plan even if
having a answer or anything and all that
is acceptable not a
problem okay uh related to that one is
medical restriction but this is also not
an insurance plan please understand not
insurance plan yes there are some
questions which are saying for example
Mr Rajiv Gupta has asked for a 69 years
old male what is the maximum Insurance
possible for five pay and say the
premium is one CR so it's not about
insurance again this plan is an
investment plan so we are not selling it
as an insurance plan so whether 69 year
old 70 year old applying for this plan
they are paying one CR per year
or let's say one CR if you're saying
about one CR divided by 83 it comes to
$120,000 per year so 120 into 5 client
is paying $600,000 in 5 years time so
$600,000 into 106 million so client is
easily getting
uh $1.25 million of accidental care
benefit in case of accident disability
happens client will going to receive
$1.25 million guaranteed and policy
continues as it is so it is an
accidental care benefit which is kind of
a rider in the Policy inbuilt rider it
is not a life insurance or anything so
there's no insurance component
here thank you Manish I hope that is
clear Mr Rajiv and everyone else please
do not confuse this with a insurance
plan okay now uh there's one last
question by Mr Jam um with foreign
exchange fluctuation the premium amount
is going to be different isn't it
correct so depending on whenever they
are paying the premium next year at that
time if INR has depreciated to 85 or 89
or 90 or appreciated to 75 or 78 so
whatever the conversion rate is
applicable client will pay premium
accordingly because because premium has
to paid in dollars not in INR and even
the maturity which is withdrawal which
is coming because in India clients
cannot maintain USD account so whenever
maturity is coming so let's take $6,000
is coming every year so the year $6,000
is coming to your account and that year
the rate whatever rate is there bank
will going to convert the amount and you
will get I equivalent irer in your
account at that time until unless India
starts okay you are easy to operate a
USD account like in morus we are free to
operate USD account or Euro account or
any other currency account so we can
keep money in USD or muur or Euro but
India has restriction for that so you
will get the converted amount only on
that day rate
applicable there is a followup question
by Mr Rajiv for one CR uh yes five year
five pay uh how much will he get so how
much he will The Client get from the
sixth year after five pay of one CR also
will it be taxable we will take the
taxable part later but let's just
address the first part I just want to
understand here Mr Raji you want to say
he's paying one CR total in five years
or he's paying one CR per year so all
depends on that so if in the question
and answer if you can put it is 1 CR
total or one CR every year for next 5
years before I answer that question okay
while he answers let's move on to the
next set of questions I have a set of
questions by Mr rupes under endowment he
has mentioned this is a statement uh
like a comment maybe not a question per
se uh and under endowment we have a
nonpar returns where the non-par returns
are guaranteed and under par returns are
not guaranteed I think he's talking
about the solutions available in India
yes correct so what you're saying that
is correct in endowment when there is a
guaranted portion so there is no
participation and when there is non
guaranted option there is a
participation option available so within
this plan so certain part is
nonparticipating which is the guaranteed
option which insurance compan is giving
every year and revisionary bonus and
terminal bonus are participating option
where client participates to generate
return because they are so okay in a way
I'll say it's a nonparticipating I can
say or a participating you can call
anything with this plan because there
are both the components available which
is guaranted component and non-
guaranted component uh both are
available in this plan one portion is
guaranted which client will receive year
on year then there are two portions
which is revisionary and terminal bonus
which is based on participating effect
where there is a participating fund of
power fund of $133
billion which is grown now in that the
returns whatever insurance company will
going to earn they pass on to their
clients so this has both non
participating and participating
component in this
plan just as a followup question to the
same uh statement rupes has as also
asked what if the revisionary bonus is
less than our expectation also is 6%
guaranteed on the whole
capital okay so coming to that when you
are withdrawing which is annuity
definitely uh that is guaranted every
year because that is coming out of the
guaranted portion and surrender of the
revisionary bonus now yes what you are
saying is correct maybe the revisionary
bonus can be less this year revisionary
bonus can be higher also revisionary
bonus can be actual also what they are
declaring so what it is shown in
illustration to you when we'll send the
illustration or I have shown in the
illustration that is what actually
insurance compan is paying year on year
currently now in certain years they pay
110% of what they are showing in certain
years they pay 98% certain years they
pay 90% certain years it is 14 % so
average is 6% year on year if you
calculate it is around 6% per
anom that's why this is the highest
sellable plan worldwide for
sunlife okay moving on I hope that
answers your question rupes um there are
few questions related to xir for this
particular solution like like please
show X in dollar denomination
and not convert into INR and uh
something with respect to that and how
is basically how is the IR return for
this particular policy as compared to
India yes as we said the IR on see why I
have converted in INR so easy for
everyone to understand if you're talking
about $115,000 or $10,000 how much is in
a client is paying because if you go to
a client in India they will not
understand
dollar how much they will be paying INR
so that's why I said that if if you're
talking about uh net return on this it
is between 5.89% to 6% annualized which
client is getting throughout the life of
the
policy so which is average around 6%
throughout the life of the policy client
going to get the net return on the
plan all right uh moving on to the next
question here there are some questions
related to
um one second customer so some of
so Mr Shiva asked sorry I'm
mispronouncing the name uh that customer
opt family me customers can opt for
family members for future benefit are
there any extra charges applicable but
in future we are actually passing on the
plan I think he's asking if there are
any charges applicable okay so for your
understanding there are no hidden
charges there are no extra charges once
policy is issued whatever premium you
are paying that premium has to be paid
for next two years or 5 years what
you're choosing there are no hidden
charges extra charges for inter wealth
transfer of policy or withdrawal or
Surrender or death benefit option
settlement CH choosing that option there
are no charges no extra charges involved
in the
policy moving to the next question Mr
Deepak is asking what is the minimum uh
sorry first of all the question is uh is
there a maximum year like by which this
can be taken entry age I think that is
one question up to what years this plan
can be taken yeah and second let me
answer for that for a 2-year plan a 80y
old person can take a plan so from zero
years up to 80 years client old client
can also op this plan and if it is a 5
pay maximum is 75 years entry age so for
2 years it is 80 years entry age and for
5 is 75 years maximum entry
age I hope that is clear Mr Deepak the
second followup question is uh how many
years of deferred uh you know the
incubation period how many years is
recommended for two years of minimum
again no again depending on client's age
like I met a client who is uh 57 years
old now if I give him a 10e deferment
period it will not going to solve his
requirement so depending on the age of a
client as an adviser I choose how to
convince a client like I shared an
example uh for a grandfather who is
paying 200,000 INR per month for uh in
mutual fund so for him I have not
decided it as an annuity plan I chose to
sell him as an uh educational plan for
his child where I told him I can pay
school fees of your child immediately
after five years when your child go your
grandchild goes into class one or class
two every month every year you will get
uh $10,000 to pay child education a
school fees and then higher studies so
depending on minimum incubation period
is for a two- pay plan from third year
onwards immediately you stop your
premium you start getting your uh nut
for 5 p is 6 year maximum how much you
want to keep depending on client's Age
and what is their expectation with this
investment like a Zimbabwe client he is
34 years old there was no point of
giving him uh money immediately on the
third year because he don't need money
at that time his kids are young he's
still earning so I thought let him get
an early retirement benefit from age 51
so I decided this all depends on
financial advisor you guys how you want
to present it to your client based on
the fact finding so minimum is
immediately after premium payment
maximum depends how you want to present
a
plan correct and
also like say for example they have
taken a two two-year plan and they say
that I want to withdraw money
immediately in the third year yes is it
possible the answer is yes it is
possible it is the the
the the money that we are putting in the
pot it is not getting enough time to
grow to get you give you significant
amount of results by that so would you
would we recom recommend it as advisers
no we will not recommend it we will
recommend wait wait wait I will answer
to this STI so if you are taking the
withdrawal immediately after the premium
payment is finished then you are getting
6% of the total amount you have
contributed but if you keep the
incubation period higher 10 years 15
years 20 years you won't get 6% your
client might get 10% of the total amount
contributed or 15% of the total amount
contributed so if you see a client who
paid $1 million he needs withdrawal from
third year onwards he's getting $6,000
so which is 6% of the uh total amount
contributed but a 34e client who
contributed again $1 million but he's
keeping 15 years and an incubation
period and taking withdrawal from 16th
year onwards he's not getting 16,000
$6,000 he's getting
$150,000 which is 15% of the total
amount contributed so higher the
incubation period higher the growth
amount and higher the withdrawal lower
the incubation period lower the growth
and lower the withdrawal amount so all
depends on that but can client withdraw
yes client can withdraw minimum what
client can get is 6% annualized per year
withdrawal yes
Sati so the next uh there are two
questions by Shan he has asked um Shan
If he if the client would like to top up
after two years or five years how much
percentage he can first of all can he
and if so then how much percentage no
client cannot as I said this plan has
only two options 2 years and 5 years
payment client has to decide in advance
how much they are contributing instead
of top up they can opt for a new policy
at that
time top up is not allowable as of
now I hope that is clear
Shan now next question
um Can this policy be sub I think this
question is very specific to an entity
not an individual can this policy be
subscribed to a company to it employ buy
a company to its employees where family
members are employees if yes what would
be the taxation applicable so I think
this this question is for a family based
business and the question is by sushan
yeah see again uh coming to that uh the
premium see policy has to be on an
individual name because there is an
accidental care benefit and all those
benefits are applicable payer benefit
and all so insured has to be an
individual can the premium be paid by
entity and all yes that option can be
explored and can be worked out that the
premium can be paid by an entity or not
that option is available and we have to
explore more opportunity with the
insurance company based on the exact
case who will be paying company will pay
what is the role of the insured in that
company director what is the income so
all those things has to be checked
taxation part again the taxation part
all the laws of in income tax are
applicable whether the plan is taken in
India or whether plan is taken outside
India same rules are
applicable yeah so so basically taxation
when it comes to taxation any capital
gain uh which you are getting out of
that policy it is taxable so you need to
understand if you are having a similar
solution in India when you get the
return if you are getting taxed in India
on INR the same thing is going to happen
in case of this policy as well the only
benefit uh you are going to get is
because the returns are in dollar so
because of dollar appreciation the
returns will be much higher so even if
there is a certain amount of tax you are
still having uh you are still being a
beneficial
position okay um there's another
question how is the client going to pay
in is the client going to pay in USD the
client can pay in INR but it'll be
converted as per that date days rate
into
USD that right Mish no client has to pay
in USD only so whenever there's a
premium due they have to give a request
to their Banker that the following
amount has to be sent uh in USD so they
will going to convert the rate prevaling
that day they will say that much INR is
required to send that much USD so they
will give a request to bank and they can
pay there is an option to pay by credit
card also if it is monthly we are
working around for that option also so
we'll come back so it automatically can
be debited from the credit card if
amount is um within the credit card
limit so we are working on the credit
card option also for monthly
payments yeah but don't uh please
understand you the client does not have
to have a dollar based account if that
was the question intent of the question
Cent dollar
account India dollar account possible so
in any case client has to pay in dollar
but dollar amount will be converted on
that applicable uh rate of that day by
the banker so whatever rate will be
there 83 82 85 70 bank will convert on
that day and tell you okay this much INR
is required to pay this much dollars
correct sanjie has asked apart from
Indian clients can I sell this plan to a
client residing in Qatar for any
nationality I would
appreciate n client start targeting them
first it's easy to sell for them uh and
you will gain experience also by selling
it to
them hands-on experience automatically
it will be very easy for you to sell in
India and I'm repeating again it is not
for every client because if you start
going and selling to some of your client
who owns a small business in
IND
dollar if you try to explain them the
dollar benefit of this plan they will
say I don't need it and they will not
going to accept whatever arguments you
will going to give them so the right
profile for this kind of a plan is Young
professional who have kids they have
study abroad they want to send their
kids to study abroad so they'll be
needing money in uh USD Now understand
reverse currency
benefit let me just give you an Insight
of that that I need money when my
daughter is right now 9 years old in
next 9 years I'll be sending her to
either Canada us or Australia or UK for
higher studies at that time I'll be
needing money in dollars or Euro or
pound or Canadian dollars but I'm
investing in inii now I'm maybe in
mutual fund I'm earning let's say 15%
per anom but by the time next 9 years my
currency INR has depreciated by 20%
so I have a minus 5% negative return on
my pocket because with the depreciated
currency I have to convert it to Dollars
and send money abroad why not to keep
certain of your investment is in dollars
itself that when you need there's no
risk on the
currency so I'm not saying that stop
selling INR plans depending on client to
client you have to judge to which client
I can propose this they have their
expectation future in dollars in other
currencies so they are the right fit for
this kind of a plan so yes nris perfect
fit for this kind of a plan yes STI yeah
moving on um the presentation yes the
presentation recording is going to be
shared we are going to do some final
editing and the team is going to share
with you so don't worry about it session
miss and or if you joined late uh we
will make sure that the presentation
recording uh reaches you so that you can
go through it and then you can come back
to us with any questions we will share
our email IDs and support IDs at the end
of the session uh there's one uh support
ID which I have shared on the chat box
can. support cfsg group.com any
illustration requests you have please
email there and our team is going to
rever to you uh like within 24 hours
okay uh moving on uh to other questions
which we
have
so is there any Financial criteria for
applying for this policy Mr chance is uh
is asking is there any criteria yes see
again yes uh when we apply for this plan
we have to justify the financial wealth
of a client so let's say example client
is showing an income of let's say
$10,000 a year but paying a premium of
$100,000 a year it doesn't fit so source
of fund requirement the income all those
things will be filled in an application
form so client's wealth has to match to
the premium what client is paying
so yes financial analysis Financial
check will be done and source of funds
will be checked and because there will
be an underwriting Financial
underwriting for the plan so when client
is applying for a policy all those
things will be
checked okay uh Mr Rajiv we have
received your illustration request
please drop that request in the email ID
that I mentioned and after this call our
team will shortly revert to you with the
quotation okay uh now moving moving on
uh to the
question can the proposer change the
second beneficiary in the plan yes at
any time beneficiaries can be changed at
any time you can have multiple
beneficiaries 10 beneficiaries
percentage of each beneficiary 5% 10%
20% but can uh the insured suppose I am
the insured I have taken a policy in my
name and I transfer the policy after 10
years in my wife name after that do I
have any Authority on the policy to
change it no once you have transferred
the authority to your wife and she
becomes the insured you don't have
control on your policy so s similar
thing you own a property after that you
do transfer the property in your son
name and you do the registry and the
your son becomes the owner of the
property do you have any control on the
property no it's your son who has a
control similar thing beneficiary yes
you can change a number of times
ownership you cannot once you transfer
the ownership you don't have control on
the policy
okay I hope that is clear uh rupes Mr
rupes had asked one question which I had
missed that when is The Accidental
benefit paid uh once like you know it is
confirmed that uh there is a diagnosis
yeah so there is a definition of the
diagnosis uh once client uh met in an
accident and has this uh disability and
uh which is continuous for 6 months uh
and doctor says that okay it is IR IR
recover Rec
recoverable uh immediately so the
insured will be receiving the amount
after the doctor Declaration on that
insurance company will going to transfer
the amount to the uh insured account so
there's a definition which I'll ask STI
to send the definition uh of that there
are terms and conditions applied on that
so it is always good to read that before
communicating it to the
client
okay um there's just few last few
questions is this product applicable
worldwide can any client across the
world take it or is there any specific
restriction okay so this plan can be
sold to any national worldwide anywhere
except us Nationals uh because there are
some trust structure issues to sell to
us clients other than then yes you can
sell it and other than the sanction
country clients like there are sanction
countries which are like Sudan South
Sudan which are war zone areas even
currently uh to the clients of uh
Ukraine Russia lebanan yes there are
some restrictions because of this war
related issues otherwise you are free to
sell it to any country
nationally so there is a country
guide but this plan there's no medical
limit or anything so it can be sold to
anyone except these countries which I
mentioned which are under war zone areas
and all
yeah there's a question that for example
if a client has taken for five years a
five pay and they pay for two years or
something and then they stop paying
they're not able to pay then what
happens to the status of the plan yeah
policy goes under lab session they can
revive it later but uh the plan starts
getting the return return even after 3
years even the guaranted benefit is
applicable after 3 years so that's why
this plan has a very short term of two
years and five years so please advise
your client only opt this plan when they
can pay for two years or 5
years um as I said there there is a
option of Premium holiday client paid
for two years and they cannot pay right
now immediately they can opt for premium
holiday for one year or two year and
they can start paying after that but
totally stop not not
advisable
yeah in which case maybe some of the
guaranteed amounts which the plan is
promising they may not be able to get is
that right Manish for that period when
they are not paying the premium so let's
take example client paid for 2 years and
cannot pay for next two years he's
opting for premium holiday for that next
two years there will be no bonuses paid
or guaranteed amount cash value paid but
client starts paying from the fifth year
onwards and pay balance three years
premium then the guarantees will be paid
and the bonuses will be
applicable okay uh this question from
deepok how much amount in USD can be
paid without any hassle for premium of
the policy in year now I'm not clear if
he's asking is what is the minimum
premium no I'll tell you no no no no no
so minimum premium to we have explained
but how much client can pay in India it
falls under lrs which is called
liberalized remittance scheme every
Indian is allowed to pay up to
$250,000 uh
remittance in dollar currency or in any
foreign currency in every year per year
now this lrs limit of 250,000 includes
Investments abroad you're taking any
policy you taking Health Plan in USD you
are traveling abroad for your leisure
time that comes under that you're uh
doing making payment for the studies of
your child that comes under uh that so
every individual every year has a limit
of
$250,000 which is allowable by Reserve
Bank of India under lrs scheme so
whatever premium you will be paying in
this plan comes under that lrs
limit great all right I think that is
pretty much it I have I missed any
question that any of you had asked I
think we have covered most of the
questions I have clubbed few questions
which were almost similar if I have
missed any question please uh last five
minutes you can put it in the Q&A
meanwhile I think the poll that Manish
had run during the second during in the
middle of the session results
but as as you can see on my screen are
you able to see my screen right now the
poll
screen yes yes yes I as you can see most
of you like uh is there a need for
dollar denominated plans in India around
83% of you have mentioned that yes there
is a need and can this be sold Almost
100% of you you agree that this can be
sold so like experts you are there in
the fields and you are there in the
market in the ground in India itself so
you already agree and you understand
that there is a need and there is a
segment for it we just need to identify
the right segment and identify their
right need and position it
so the solution is this yeah I I will
add up what STI is saying this plan is
not for everyone this plan is for a
niche market a limited market who
understands the benefit of having
investment in hardcore currency
if you are selling it to them maybe it
is not advisable for them it is not
beneficial for them they don't
understand benefit but a businessman a
young professional those who understand
the importance of having a investment in
foreign currency how it can be utilized
in future for themselves for their kids
for their family yes this plan makes
sense for them and I have lot of clients
in India who have invested in such
plans because I'm from India market I've
worked in Indian Insurance Market I
understand Insurance products deep
whatever are there in India market in
Global Market and uh even I had this
thought when I initially started working
in this field of offshore products
he why they will going to buy but for
last five years I'm selling it in Indian
market and people are paying premiums
worth Dollars around $100,000 per year
people are paying premium in insurance
plans or investment plans or health
plans people are paying premium because
they understand the benefit so you have
to look for a right fit clientele for
this kind of a
product yes Sai okay amazing uh we don't
have any more questions I think uh we
are going to share the link of uh the
presentation recording everything um
Nisha do we have uh the final poll we
just want to run one final poll to get I
want you to share only one key takeaway
from the session actually I'll do one
thing Nisha it's okay let me share one
link here and I want to see what you
have in your mind
everyone
minute
okay
is everyone able to click on this
link I think Mr Gupta wants to ask some
question he has raised his
hand okay Mr Gupta can you just type
your question on the if I missed your
question can you type it in the
Q&A Mr Gupta Could you type your
question on the Q&A please if you don't
mind okay and the question now you
should be able to see the
question please click on the link on the
screen you should be able to see a
question I just need one ke key takeaway
from this
session okay I am going to share my
screen if you can allow me Manish I'm
going to see here are the responses
which are popping
up I'm stop sharing my screen you
can yeah is everyone able to see my
screen
yes
one key takeaway from this from this
session and what you have understood
what you are taking back to your clients
uh basis we are going to reach out if
you have shared your client profiles if
you have shared illustration requests we
are definitely going to look at it and
Manish is going to personally get in
touch with some of the shortlisted uh
requests that have come and we are going
to announce their names as well in the
group
available from age zero yes that's right
it has high return savings that's
correct uh sunlife yes sun lifee has
been in this market
forever
imag inbuilt Legacy feature that is
correct generational yes it is a
intergenerational uh uh uh plan where
you can actually where the parent or the
policy owner can transfer it for
Generations I just I just want to add up
one thing I like uh J
one more option see I always believe in
that you should have a bouet
of plans with
you something new you should have to go
back one more thing that if you have any
plan in India which you are taking to
your client there are several other
advisers who have similar kind of plans
from other insurance companies and
offering same to your client so let's
say guaranted income plan sdfc is
selling Sun Max life is selling their
own guaranted income plan Reliance is
selling their own guaranted all the
insurance companies have similar plan
but with this plan you have one thing
unique no other adviser can offer this
plan if you have same so this kind of a
monopoly you will going to have with
these kind of solutions but you have to
find the right fit of your client so yes
you have one more option to propose to
your client which no other adviser can
sell and your client can't say okay okay
no no no I got similar option from XYZ
financial adviser or oh that client that
adviser also came to offer me this so
this is unique you only have access to
this kind of a plant or very limited
advisers in India has access to these
kind of plans absolutely okay I'll stop
thank you so much for your inputs it is
actually
insightful that you are taking some
value out of this uh and we will be so
much glad to help you out stand out in
the
market
already and when you take this as a
solution you stand out especially
specific Niche
segment this this is how you will be
actually unique
us I'll stop sharing my screen there is
the last question which I think Mr Rajiv
had asked um this is pertaining to the
to the sunlife statistics that Manish
you had shared $137 billion is total AUM
of sunlife or is this the funds AUM no
this is the participating fund AUM where
they make investment in these kind of
plans so there are multiple booket list
of plans like sanjoy there are other
plans also so all the investment of
these plan goes into
$33.7 billion which was as of end of
2021 which has grown now so later
figures are awaited we will share with
you so all these plan investment goes in
this participating fund now every plan
has their unique strategy of that fund
so for sanjoy plan there is only 5%
Equity exposure maybe there's another
plan Omare which has 40% Equity exposure
there is another plan Sun product which
might have 50% Equity exposure So within
participating fund also there are
different different strategies for each
plan so yes this is an a of
participating fund where the investment
is made this is not a total a of
sunlife that is multi-billion dollar
a thank you Manish I hope that is clear
Mr Rajiv uh I do not see any more
questions in the Q&A box in which case
I'm assuming that s
questions will try to revert we will uh
we'll be sharing the recording so
everyone who has missed it uh they
should go through it we will have uh a
Q&A session in future maybe uh but for
sanjoy this is one session for this
particular quarter um the for next
session is uh with respect to another
saving solution next week which is
called investor trust that is also a
very good solution and I encourage you
to please attend that session uh Manish
if you can just share a few words about
that solution in your in your words then
that will be helpful and uh for the
audience no no definitely see again
whatever Solutions Continental will
going to bring you those will be unique
Solutions which is not available in the
Indian market so the next session which
SWAT is talking about the investor trust
plan it is again a guaranteed uh return
return plan investment plan guaranteed
return plan with an option of investment
for 15 years or 20 years so it's a
long-term investment some clients want
to invest a smaller amount for but for
longterm so you clients has an option
and there is a inbuilt guarantee in the
plan that minimum client will going to
get this much amount after 15 years or
20 years or depending on the investment
of the market which is linked to S&P 500
Index so guaranteed income plan yes
security yes long-term strategy yes all
those features are there in this plan so
attend the session to know from the
experts of those plans that how it will
going to work for you and for
your absolutely and this again that
session will be taken by one of the
experts from the company from the
provider company itself so please make
sure that you you know keep that slot
open for you next week
again you process all the information
that you have and then we will come back
to you in February sessions calendar and
just to add up just to add up what STI
is saying if some of you actually has
some of a CL Cent you think that can fit
into this kind of a product can fit into
that and I know you don't have that
experience to go to the client and
present it very well so we are available
for you if you want to have one-on-one
session with us you want to have a joint
call with your client yes definitely we
will going to help you out and we will
ensure that uh if the case is positive
we will ensure that we can close the
case for
you can cannot get any better person who
can actually handhold you and help you
close a case so I think it's a good
opportunity if you have clients please
share I hope you have already shared
that information in the client profile
link that I put it in the chat uh we
will connect with you based on the
profiles that you have shared we will be
more than happy to have one toone
conversations where Manish is going to
guide them and we are
also Partners who uh really want our us
to be present in the zoom call while
they are presenting to their clients we
are happy to be there as well as much as
support you need we will do we will
share that with
you all right uh any last uh words if
not we will close the call thank you so
much for your time everyone I know it is
a middle of the week it has been busy uh
beginning of the year L uh you all took
out time to attend the session and it
just shows your dedication and your
interest for what uh Continental has
promised you you uh thank you once again
and we appreciate it very much thank you
everyone have a good day and very good
week thank you STI thank you everyone
bye thank you